

NGUYỄN ĐĂNG NGỌC HIỆP

FULL-STACK DIGITAL MARKETING

Contact

Phone: 0877 39 79 99

Mail: johnnyhiepnguyen@gmail.com

Address: Binh Tan District, TPHCM CV online: jmehiepp.github.io My Blog: hiepnguyen.io.vn

Expertise

- Digital/web development
- Copywriting
- Analysing customer data insight
- Affiliate marketing
- · Direct marketing
- Social media
- Marketing automation & integration
- Optimising campaigns
- Optimising Customer/user experience

Language

Vietnamese

English

About Me

" One of the key factors that helps me absorb knowledge better, learn Ask questions faster and connect things more easily comes from growth mindset technology. I understand SEO but also dig into the web with self-taught HTML/CSS/Javascript, I know how to set up ads but also understand how to use them in practice by an advertising background, I know how to write content. I also understand how content is measured and tracked across platforms, etc. I started my career from a piece of knowledge and extended it to other asymptotic areas. And struggle to add to the knowledge of the fields by self-study or experience with projects .."

Skills









Experience

HoclaiotoNET 2021-2023

Marketing Manager

- Develop monthly and quarterly marketing strategies for the company
- Cooperate with Kols, Celebrity, run direct advertising program & digital marketing, combine affiliate marketing program
- Synthesize and analyze reports, update the latest advertising methods and offer the optimal plan and customer file for advertising
- Implement optimal advertising based on platforms: Facebook, Tiktok, Zalo, Instagram with a budget of approximately 2 billion VND/month
- · Coordinate and review content with content creator, design and media teams to distribute promotional content, HoclaiotoNET social channels: Facebook, Tiktok, Youtube, Website

Yody 2020 - 2021

Facebook Advertising Specialist & E-Commerce Platform Operation Specialist

- Run Facebook ads for The Moon team, convert to messages, traffic to e-commerce shop
- Building an e-commerce shop on shopee and lazada platforms: **YODY CLOTHES**
- · Manage and organize minigames, cashback programs, build customer groups and fanpages

Education

2016-2019

Dong Nai Technical College

Majors: Information Technology

Good

2020

GTV SEO

Complete the SEO MASTERMIND course

